Ooishi-san
Because inbound recovery is expected, I have set up the Japanese content
Can you please take a look?
Okay, I'll take a look
I'm sorry
Can you you make the name of the star bigger?
Hey, how is the media coverage for tomorrow's supplement company launch going to be?
Yesterday's special show about Ichiro teaching baseball to kids was great
Summer equals Koushien after all
Sweat, mud and tears melts together under the summer sun, right?
That's right
But Chief, playing sports under
the blazing hot sun is kind of outdated don't you think?
Just the other day it was 30 degrees in the middle of the night
I thought that my phone was broken
Singing the school anthem to support their school at the Alps stand
That's youth for you
That's summer in Japan for you
You think so too, Kirimura-san?
Is it global warming? Or is it the pole shift?
I don't remember my school anthem
Don't you think that it's absurd that the temperature setting for air conditioning the whole building is the same for all floors?
It depends on the season, only during summers and winters
Your generation also watches Koushien, right Komukai?
I want to see kids keep looking at the sky
I agree
It's certainly a bit chilly over here
Do you want to file a complaint?
You watch Koushien, right Komukai?
At least reply when people are talking to you
Is this also a power harassment, huh?
What?
I'm sorry
What is it?
No, it's nothing
It sure is peaceful over here
That's right
So precious
Okay, it's time
Okay
As you know,
due to the wave of digitalization
the event industry is in transition
I want everyone to respond accordingly just like Ooishi-kun
I'm counting on you, Ooishi-kun
I'll do my best
Thank you very much
Ooishi-san is good looking, don't you think?
I'm not interested in him at all
Ooishi-kun sure is getting fat
Just like Inuzuka-kun in his younger days
I was just greasy back then
They should have done this award ceremony over Zoom
You're just the best Ooishi-san
There's an interesting freshman in department 1
Nobody is getting assigned to be under me in department 3, right?
Next up is the joint project presentation
Department 1 proposes an IoT project in depopulated areas
This is a medium-to-long-term city development project
We will strive for regional revitalization through IoT
Department 2 proposes
a metaverse avatar fashion show
A famous person's avatar will appear on the show,
so you can enjoy an exclusive experience
In the metaverse that is all the rage these days...
What department 3 came up with is
a cat park where you can interact with cats
We will prepare a number of attractions while they are playing the the cute cats
Komukai
What the hell are you doing?
Getting hot water
That's not what I'm asking you
The joint presentation, what was that all about?
The cat park?
Was that a joke?
Or are you guys for real?
We came up with a project, it's all good
Don't you think that it's not good to just come up with something to clear your quota?
What are you talking about?
Think about moving people and money in your head
You've got to give it all that you got
Work using your own name
Are you okay with just by getting your paycheck?
Did I did something to you, Asai?
You said during the entrance ceremony to do our best because we don't have that many people that enter the company at the same time
I did?
I'm tired watching department 3
What's wrong with you?
Were you eavesdropping, Nakano-san?
I just overheard on my way to get some coffee
Department 3 is the only one in red
So unpleasant
Your project is interesting, but I just can't see it actually happening
Have you evaluated your own project?
If you take what others have told you and then you tell other people as is, I'm going to punch you
It's okay to be passionate, but do it yourself
Komukai
Why are you looking at your phone?
Today's lunch
You...
Since when you become a mass production-type person?
Mass production-type?
Working under the radar, avoiding conflicts,
getting your paycheck,
looking forward to lunch all the time
and then posting said lunch on a SNS site that nobody sees
That's out of line
You know just how hard the event industry is, right?
The way things are going, there's a rumor that department 3 is getting disbanded
What?
I thought that everything would be fine if I'm here, but...
An organization spreads those kinds of rumors from time to time...
Mass production-type
They might ask me to retire early
I guess I'll move somewhere when the time comes
Background character
NPC
I want to stay here forever, because it's peaceful
Kijimura-san
We still don't know what the future holds
Everyone
Let's do everything that we can for our client
Manten Nodoame's event
Can't this be a DM instead?
It's our love for Manten Nodoame
That's right
Our thoughts and feelings will reach them
What's up with that friend of yours, Asai?
I think that he has a strong desire for approval
Agreed
Nakano-san
Yes?
Am I a mass production-type person?
What makes you happy?
When I chill out at home
Why?
Because it's fun
What do you want to be in the future?
The future...
What about you, Nakano-san?
I want to be rich
As expected from you
I want to maintain the status quo as much as possible
Is there something that you want?
A good hair dryer
Club activities?
I was in the dance club during middle school
and I didn't join any clubs in high school
You like to dance?
Everyone was doing it at the time
What about college?
Literature department, majoring in German literature
What attracted you to German literature?
It was the easiest department to get into
Tell me your war story
I never missed a day of cram school
What about the election?
I don't have an interest, but I do vote
Where do you buy your clothes?
I bought them all at the train station
Yup...
You're a mass production-type person
I see
A mass production-type Riko with no peaks nor valleys
That's even worse that what Asai said to me
Forgive me
Don't stop working
I'm sorry
Oh yeah, can I do my own work now?
The one from the second division, right?
Okay, please help her
Okay
A rare store festival
What is that?
You know that there used to be a lot of independent stores like electric, stationary and candy stores in town,
but they're all now few and far between, right?
This project aims to show off the uniqueness of such retro spaces
Seeing the trophies at the hardware store gets my blood pumping
For me...
I loved the toy store
I felt like everything in that store was waiting for me
My heart was racing every time I passed it
Everything was sparkling
I was interested in things like robots, plastic models, or dinosaurs
But I was nervous every time I passed it for some reason
I was excited looking at dolls or transforming sticks
A mass production-type where she has lost her dreams, huh?
Please don't say that
Just kidding
Anyway, if you see such a store, go take a look, okay?
Okay
Good work
Since when you become a mass production-type person?
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing
Excuse me
Komukai
Yes?
Are you making a fool of yourself?
What?
Are you excited?
Is excitement necessary for adults?
I heard what he said to you earlier
Is there anything that you can get lost in?
Playing Pokemon or watching videos
Do you like that so much that it makes your nose bleed?
No
You should go wild, so much so that it will make your nose bleed
Thank you very much
Go wild
What?
Go wild?
What did he mean by "go wild"?
What is a mass production-type?
Toy store
I didn't know there was a toy store here
Model store?
Last shooting
You must be surprised, I'm terribly sorry
It's okay
How many times have I told you to turn on the lights once it gets dark, Yassan?
What are you looking for?
I'm not here because I'm looking for something
Do you like plastic models?
I've never built one before
It's your first time, huh?
No, I just entered this store on a whim
On a whim...
That's fine
Please take your time and choose a plastic model
You have plenty of time
Thank you very much
Mass production-type
It's a mobile suit from the anime Mobile Suit Gundam that's used by the enemy force, the Zeon army:
Main mass production-type Zaku
Zaku
You know Gundam, right?
Only the name
Because Zaku is a mass production-type, it has no discerning trait and people say that it's a background character
Not only for combat, but it is also used for security, large-scale construction and reconnaissance
In short, they serve as the foil to other distinct and strong mobile suits
Foils...
But, one reason that Gundam is a long beloved series
A lot of these type of mass production-type appeared on screen
So the production gives a sense of reality that there are ordinary soldiers that fought in wars
On top of it,
For on land or for underwater use
The charm of a mass production-type is that it has a lot of variations
and because of that, people are still going crazy over it to this day
The charm of a mass production-type...
That's right
I want to build it
Is that so?
Do you want to build this over there?
What?
It's free of charge
I'm going to pay for it
It's rare to see someone chose an old kit
Old kit?
It was the start of everything
It's the start of Gunplas
What is your name?
Komukai Riko
Okay then Riko-san
Please go
Go?
Go, Riko!
Okay
Riko is off
Open the box
The thing that the parts are attached to is called a runner
Pretty, isn't it?
But it only has one color
You're going to paint it
Paint?
Let's get started
You cut the part that connects the parts to the runner, they are called gates
Don't worry about the order this time
just start cutting wherever you want
Released
Bring it to life
Carefully
That is a 1/144 mass production-type Zaku
That is an old type of plastic model called old kit
All the parts must be glued together
The age range was changed from 8 years old and up to 15 years old and up
That's a lot of information
Okay
Next up is gluing the parts
The newer models are snap fit and don't need any glue,
but it is needed for old kits
It's glue for plastic models
This is the first time using it
I put too much glue on it
Don't worry, you can smooth it out later
Smooth it out?
That's right
I broke it
There's nothing that you can do about number 41
Chiemi
Yes
You continue building it, Riko
No honorifics?
It's done
What should I do next?
We wait until the glue is dry
We wait?
Okay
Now we're going to smooth out the excess glue
It's time to do the head
Now it's time to paint the Zaku
Usually you paint it while looking at the box
Failure is sometimes a gift
You can fix it to your heart's content
To my heart's content...
You can do anything with plastic models
There is no rule that says you have to paint it like the box
Normally, you'd temporarily build it first before painting it to figure out the spots that is hard to paint over
I'll teach you about that later
The old kits...
Mass production-type Zaku
Give birth!
Give birth
Congratulations
It felt like sound disappeared for a moment
It's because of the amygdala that is located deep within your brain was working
That part of the brain is usually tired because of information overload, but
When you can concentrate on just one thing, you feel energized and is able to concentrate
You were in the zone
I feel like I'm going to get a nose bleed
What the heck
So funny
They say that they can see the story just by looking at a masterpiece plastic model
Mine is clunky so I don't see the story at all, but...
But...
Yes?
It's really cute
Fondness is a form of love
It's your very own mass production-type Zaku that you built yourself
My very own mass production-type Zaku
Thank you very much
Don't mention it
Come again!
Did something happen, Riko?
I'm going to deliver these documents
I'm terribly sorry
You were too aggressive
Think it over and don't worry about it
Komukai-san
Yes
About the cat park that you presented during the joint presentation
There's not a lot of people who can pull it off
Do your best
Thank you very much
It's not like I was scolded, got it?
I didn't think you were
department 3 might come to an end soon
A problematic person from department 1 is coming your way
Asai
Do you remember what you told me the other day?
What?
I'm Komukai Riko, a mass production-type person
You...
What are you saying with a straight face...
Hey!
Komukai...